EVA KRAMER

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

https://github.com/EvaKra

• London

+447517430121

≥ eva.kramer91@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/eva-kramer

INTRODUCTION

After 4 years in various commercial roles being exposed to working with tech teams, I have decided to change my career path and become a web developer.

I successfully completed a 9week intense coding bootcamp at Le Wagon and I am looking forward to continue learning about new technologies, languages and frameworks.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Ruby on Rails
- APIs, JSON, scraping
- Relational databases, SQL, PostgreSQL
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- ES6 Javascript
- Wireframes, prototyping, UI
- Test driven development
- · Git, Github, technical workflow

LANGUAGES

- German (native)
- English (fluent, IELTS 7.5)

PROJECTS

Designed, implemented and shipped to production:

- Travelizer (ongoing) Web app that allows users to create travel itineraries and share these with the travel community.
- Recyclable As a team of four within two weeks we built a web app that helps consumers to identify whether a specific piece of packaging can be recycled. It also offers alternative product suggestions to help users make better purchasing decisions in the future.
- Rento Web app enabling users to rent and rent out a variety of items in their neighbourhood.

Built using Ruby on Rails, Javascript, ¡Query, AJAX, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, ActiveRecord, APIs, Github and Heroku.

EXPERIENCE

ASSOCIATE VICE PRESIDENT, ACCOUNT MANAGEMENT

Third Bridge, London 02/2019 - 11/2019

- Increased annual revenue across client portfolio in EMEA by 16% YoY
- Signed two new clients offices and manged client lifecycle including effective on-boarding, usage monitoring, early risk identification and business value reviews
- Liaised with the product team and ran client demos to implement new application features

SENIOR ASSOCIATE, ACCOUNT MANAGEMENT

Third Bridge, London 10/2017 - 01/2019

- Hosted client user training and demos as well as provided inbound support to consulting clients
- Identified inactive users on priority accounts and used product offering to engage clients, including cross-selling products through a variety of media

E-COMMERCE - SALES & OPERATIONS EXECUTIVE

VisitBritain, London 10/2015 - 09/2017

- Updated content for the German Shop through a CMS
- Rolled out a new products across all VisitBritain Shops including all steps from sourcing the product to putting it live on the website
- Completed full month end financial processes for the German online shop
- Forecasted sales figures of Visitor Oyster Cards and Travelcards across all VisitBritain shops

EDUCATION

CODING BOOTCAMP AT LE WAGON LONDON, 01/2020 - 03/2020

9-week intensive coding bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails.

UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES WORMS, GERMANY

B.A. Tourism and Travel Management 10/2012 - 07/2015

- Dissertation topic: Economic aspects of the tertiary sector in Germany
- Semester abroad at European Business School London